Clean water and breathable air,
the promise of which is a fundamental human right.
EVA Solutions has been keeping that promise alive
for over a decade since
founder Desmond Frey's unveiling
of the very first EVA prototype
to the EVA units used today.
A drop of hope in a world of desperation. EVA.
Lights on.
Ambient temperature, 23 degrees Celsius. AQI, 151.
Laura.
There she is.
How'd you sleep?
Good. You? - Good.
Good.
Gotta stay inside today. Index is 150.
Dad, please.
Air quality index over 125, I gotta ground you.
You know that.
Am I getting worse?
No.
No, it's just precautionary. Hey, chin up.
We could work on one of our projects today.
You got the part?
Not exactly, but there has been a plan
that's been put into motion.
I think I found a way into his compound.
Just need a little time.
These guys think they own
everything. The air, the water.
What's next?
Let's keep you on extra water until you improve.
What about yours?
I'll be fine this morning.
Inhale.
Exhale. Warrior two.
Inhale. Hold.
Exhale. Lower down.
Inhale. Pull through.
Press back. Down dog.
Inhale. Rise.
Exhale. Fold.
Step right foot forward.
Inhale.
Rise. Warrior two.
Find focus.
End sequence.
Namaste, Desmond.
And more about
the situation here.
First, let's go live to Emma Evans in the field.
Hi, Genevieve.
I'm here on location in downtown Los Angeles
where protesters are angry about the failed vote
to... Hey.
It's a little too early for that, don't you think?
We're supposed to be saving water, remember?
Okay.
This is filter compound test number 107.
Beginning water purification test.
Primer ready. Starting synthesis.
Toxicity level dropping.
Toxins parts per million?
20,000 and dropping.
Energy's neutralising.
Keep an eye on radiation levels before the PPM drops.
Let me know when.
Now.
PPM at 10,000...
Filter failure.
Water toxicity above safe consumption threshold.
It's okay.
There's still the EVA beta.
The FOV was on the fritz, so I had to reset it.
Seems like it's working now.
No substitute for the whole thing, I guess, though, huh?
I'll put in a service request.
So, you meeting with the board today?
Board?
You mean the guys who I
made rich over the last 10 years
and now they want to push me out of my own company?
No matter what, you know I support you, right?
You've worked so hard to build all of this.
You did that, for us.
And it's great and I love it, but we don't need any of this.
I'm good either way.
I know.
Okay, well, anyways,
I'm gonna head out for a bit, so I'll see you later, yeah?
Yeah. See you later. - Good.
Why don't you come with me?
You know, get out of this fortress.
The real world does still exist.
Maybe next time, okay?
The position isn't so cut and dry.
However, Mr. Frey is a visionary, a genius, if you will.
But to fix these issues takes strategy,
rationing, implementing laws, and so on.
Shareholders are getting
weary of the constant bad news.
That's not good for EVA or anyone else.
New residents losing hope
that as development slows
and land ownership appeals...
Who claim that EVA is selling water
to the highest bidder.
You okay?
If you're thirsty, we could get some water
from rations, just for today.
No thanks, Dad. I'll be fine for today.
I have their best interests at-
Clean water is a basic human right.
Would you plan to make this available to everyone?
I'm gonna go take a shower.
Why don't you get ready for bed?
It's a simple question.
Mr. Frank? I mean, ballpark.
Sonic chamber initialising.
Breaking news.
In a sudden move, EVA Solutions founder and CEO,
Desmond Frey, met with board members today
and announced intentions to leave the company
and relinquish his controlling
shares to the next owner.
No... - Emma.
Genevieve, while this is a new development,
the questions and concerns
regarding the source code
for the EVA-
Dad? - Technology remain.
What is known
is that Mr. Frey will be leaving EVA Solutions.
Many expect shareholder
fallout from creating room
for the new leadership to craft a future...
Good night, Angel, I love you.
Good night, Mr. Frey.
Good morning, Desmond. Starting morning sequence.
Visitor. Front door.
Maintenance tech alpha, 1756.
He's here to fix the FOV.
I never sent a request.
Oh, it was an automatic request.
Well, you got it?
I'll be upstairs.
I'm alpha one... No.
Alpha 1756, I'm sorry.
That was rude.
I'm Desmond.
No problem. I'm George.
Incoming call. Urgent.
George, I have to take this.
Can you find your way there?
The panel is over there by the FOV.
Incoming call. Urgent. - Yes, sir.
You all done?
Uh, yeah.
Let's grab a drink.
Oh, I don't drink.
I insist.
You like the view? I had other options, you know.
Martian colonies, the floating
cities in the clean zone.
But I chose this place.
I guess something about it reminds me of the part
of my life that once was.
Of course it all looks different now.
Of course.
You wanna know how I got to where I am?
It was George, right? Know how I got where I am, George?
Eight years ago, I designed the first EVA device.
The EVA beta.
It was the first working
prototype that would lead us
to the EVA pure units today.
I keep it here where I can see it every day to remind me.
You have any idea what it takes to start a company?
The magnitude of sacrifice?
It's amazing.
You should be very proud. Thanks for the water.
But I really should be going. But yeah, it's...
Beautiful?
Yes, it is. This construction is impeccable.
Honestly, the design is flawless.
It's a wonderfully tooled replica.
It's incredible, but something like this just
has a soul that can't be replicated.
I knew the second I saw it.
Security is already on its way.
I'm assuming mine's in the bag there.
Why don't we go ahead and
put that back where it belongs?
Though I got to ask you,
why steal something that only has meaning to me?
You have no idea what this represents. The work.
The ingenuity it took to create.
You see, that's the difference between you and me.
That's why I am where I am.
No.
No?
This is the difference between you and I.
For you it's all about money and profit. But to us?
It's about life and death. And sacrifice?
You can talk to me about sacrifice?
Have you ever had to ration your water?
Water that if you drank it would just make you sick?
You'd die from dehydration if you didn't?
Yeah, if we had one of your EV units we'd be fine.
But no one can afford it.
They don't even have them in our quadrants.
And even if they did we'd
have to keep getting new filters.
It's a never-ending uphill battle.
I don't understand.
What did you come here for today?
I don't have the technology
to reverse engineer the new units.
So I needed the source code from the original.
Reverse engineer?
Do you have any idea how complex the design is?
I figured most of it out, Desmond.
It's photocatalytic elements.
I just can't figure it out how you protected
the plasma-facing elements in the edge region
while powering the synthesis.
That's why I needed the source code. That's why I'm here.
You know when I started this company
it wasn't about the money.
But there are so many things
that stand in the way, George.
You have no idea.
This wasn't my intention. Any of this.
I have a daughter.
She's not well. This was my only option.
Take it. - Excuse me?
The EVA beta.
Take it. I had a daughter too.
A long time ago.
I admire your tenacity.
Go ahead. Security won't stop you.
What was your daughter's name?
Eva.
FOV, deactivate.
Field of view shutting down.
Look what I found.
I told you not to eat like that. Fuel, not food.
Better.
We have to get going.
You stand a better chance without me.
We're doing this together.
Do you trust this claim or not?
I don't really have a choice.
I thought you lot were supposed
to have the answer to everything.
I'm not flying, remember?
Don't smile.
It's human.
Better.
I told you. You can't afford to be tired or hurting.
Is there a way of teaching me these things
without hurting me?
It's not personal.
I've shown you how to shut down your mental
and physical impulses.
Cosmetics alone won't get you in.
Soften your expression.
Better.
We're not all built anatomically perfect
like you.
Shall we give them some food?
Come.
It's healthy. What are you doing?
Spots. - Not for you?
Get in. - What are you doing?!
Get in!
Hey! - Hey!
What are they doing! - Hey!
Get out of our car!
Hey! What are they doing!
What are you doing?
Drive!
I can't believe it. Are you okay?
Your face is betraying your thoughts.
We took their home.
This is not a home, it's a vehicle.
They can make another shelter.
I know you feel emotion.
Feeling and showing is not the same.
I thought this place was supposed to be overflowing
with people.
Some died, some returned.
Only some get in.
Can you still help my sister?
You're gonna need a lot of work.
Here, can you stir that for me?
Why did you learn all this?
Even when you were through,
any sign of emotion will ground you a radical.
You're there on their terms.
Once denied, they will never let you in.
What else do I need to know?
You do not need to know anything.
Knowledge is not necessary.
Humanity is not necessary.
Humanity is back there killing themselves.
That is why you must take the girl, as promised.
When we have our status, we will come back for her.
I'm trusting you.
We'll be back for her.
This is going to be cold.
Forward.
Go through. - Can I wait?
Go through.
Forward.
We'll be back for her.
Memories are like dreams.
They take us far away, to moments lost in time.
They're imperfect, just like us.
But my memories are nightmares I can't unsee.
In the darkness of my mind my mother lives on.
But so does the monster that took her away from me.
Mommy...
Then I will find him.
You shouldn't be here.
Are you alright?
Hey, look at me. You're gonna be fine.
Find a way out.
This place is a mess.
He's watching us.
Halt.
Collins.
We have to get out of here before it's too late.
It's only gonna get worse.
Johnson?
How do you know?
I've been here before.
Pay attention.
Mommy.
Daddy?
Lauren.
Baby.
It was never you fault.
Are you alright?
Lauren?
We can't change our past.
We can remember, forget, move on.
How are you feeling? - Dreams, nightmares.
They all end the same way. We just need to open our eyes.
And after all this time, I'm finally awake.
Laura.
Hebrah? Is it you?
Yes.
We were told...
We thought we lost you.
How is Naira? - Holding on.
She misses you so very dearly.
We'll all be over soon.
I've spoken to the others.
We are close to making a push.
Just tell me when and where.
We'll be ready.
Look for the lights in the sky.
Come to the spot with her.
5718. Surrender yourself.
Hello?
Hebrah? - Are you at the location?
Yes.
Yes, we are here.
No!
Wait.
Do you think the others made it out?
Breaking down the wall was just the start.
For so long, hybrids like me
were torn from our parents
and had to hide because people were scared of us.
Now, I'm back with my family.
And I wish everyone would one day see that love
is stronger than fear.
Hi, mom. It's been a while.
We've been touring village after village, as usual.
Yesterday we got called in to help out at a village
that was under heavy fire.
We helped get these kids out of a school.
And then when we reunited them with their families,
it started snowing.
It never snows here. It reminded me of home.
And of you and dad.
I just wanted to let you know I was thinking of you.
I love you, mom. Bye.
I love you, mom...
Okay. Let's see.
Wow.
Hi.
Hello.
I am Sheila.
Shilah. - Sheila.
Shilah. - Better.
It'll come. It's very nice to meet you.
Fist bump? High five?
Oh.
Cool.
I am... - Oh, Melo.
I know. It's a lovely name.
All right, then. There's a lot that I have to show you.
Follow me.
Sheila.
You're the smartest girl I know.
Yeah. Both you and your daddy.
I can help you blow these out. Ready?
One, two, three.
I know.
I love you too, honey. Eight.
Sheila. - How did you
get to be so big.
Your hair is so soft.
This is great.
Oh my gosh. Melo, what are you doing?
Is dinner ready? Okay.
I'll be right there.
♪ I never planned falling in love with you ♪
♪ I never planned falling ♪
That's so sweet of you,
but I need this glass for drinking.
Oh.
Oh, don't look so sad, silly.
It's okay.
♪ Always thought forever ♪
♪ I wanted to ♪
♪ This wonderful life of mine ♪
That's snow.
Wow.
My daughter, she loves snow more
than anything else.
♪ And knowing the storm... ♪
Speaking of my daughter, you, my new friend,
are in for a real treat.
Do you like it?
Yeah.
My daughter and my husband,
they used to sit together at
that piano for hours every day.
Could you teach me?
Why not?
We're going to begin with scales.
Ah, uh, hmm.
Okay.
So one finger at a time.
Start with your thumb on C.
Right there. And it looks and sounds like this.
My husband learned this faster than you are. It's okay.
It's all right. Try again.
Come on. We'll do it together.
Thumb on C. Ready?
Keep practising. Okay?
Mm-hmm.
Come on, come on, come on.
Hmm...
Mm...
Julia? - Hi, Mom.
If you get this message, well, you know,
there's so much I wanna say to you.
Happy holidays.
I got you that robot as a present because I've heard
that they're really good companions.
Better than me. I haven't been around for you lately.
Oh, yeah.
I wish I could be there with you right now.
I wish I could just...
Mom?
I'm forever grateful for everything you've done.
I never realised I would miss those moments so much.
I wanna come home.
I love you, mom.